(Amy(answering phone):)Sheldon, what's wrong?
(Sheldon:)I wanted to let you know I'll be
spending your birthday with you.
(Amy:)Okay.
See, I-I had tickets to the
Star Wars premiere that night,
(Sheldon:)but Professor Proton came to me
in a dream dressed as
(Sheldon:)Obi-Wan Kenobi and convinced me
I should be with you.
(Amy:)Obi-what?
I'll-I'll let you get back
to sleep now. Good night.
(Amy:)Okay. Good night. Wait.
(Amy:)Um, Sheldon,
were you actually not gonna
spend my birthday with me?
(Sheldon:)It's late. Got to go. Bye.
(Raj:)Good for Sheldon deciding
(Raj:)to stay with Amy on her birthday.
I know.
(Leonard:)It's still gonna be weird
to see the movie without him.
(Howard:)Well, we could wait a
couple days and see it together.
(loud laughter)
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Leonard:)Hey. We're going to the comic
book store. You want to come?
(Sheldon:)No, I can't.
(Sheldon:)I need to make preparations
for Amy's birthday.
(Sheldon:)Which leads me
(Sheldon:)to the following bit
of business.